<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ______                   ______  _                             _     _       _                         
 / _____)                 (_____ \| |                           | |   | |     | |                        
| /  ___  ____ ____   ____ _____) ) | ____ _   _  ____  ____ ___| |__ | |_   _| | _     ____  ___  ____  
| | (___)/ _  |    \ / _  )  ____/| |/ _  | | | |/ _  )/ ___)___)  __)| | | | | || \   / ___)/ _ \|    \ 
| \____/( ( | | | | ( (/ /| |     | ( ( | | |_| ( (/ /| |  |___ | |   | | |_| | |_) )_( (___| |_| | | | |
 \_____/ \_||_|_|_|_|\____)_|     |_|\_||_|\__  |\____)_|  (___/|_|   |_|\____|____/(_)\____)\___/|_|_|_|
                                          (____/                                                         

File:     aboutPage.xml
Author:   Peter DiSalvo
Date:     April 2012

Purpose:  Page is well-formed XHTML that is styled by a separate styler page (about.xml), so the XLST
          processor can change the file extensions for the navigation links.
-->
<html>
<head>
    <title>Game Players Hub</title>
    <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="GPHStyles.css" />
</head>
<body>
    <header>
        <div id="headerContent">
            <p id="tagLine">
                Video game news, reviews and a place to be heard.</p>
            <div id="navWrapper">
                <nav>
                    <a href="about.html">About</a>
                    <a href="articles.html">Articles</a>
                    <a href="games.html" class="current">Games</a>
                    <a href="index.html">Home</a>
                </nav>
            </div>
        </div>
    </header>
    <div id="headerBottomDivider">
    </div>
    <div id="headerBottomShadow">
    </div>
    <section id="mainContent">
    <h1>
        About GamePlayersHub</h1>
    <p>
        GamePlayersHub is a source for video game news and reviews. Video game reviews are
        rated on a percentage scale. You may notice that the scores are colored differently.
        The colors are based on the visible light spectrum to go with the galactic theme.
        Isn't that great? If you're still thinking about that one, the answer is "yes, it's
        great". Moving on... The colors for ratings are attributed based on the red-shift
        and blue-shift observed in the Doppler Effect. When a light source moves away from
        an observer the electromagnetic wavelength increases causing it to shift toward
        the red end of the spectrum, conversely when a light source moves toward an observer
        the electromagnetic wavelength decreases causing it to shift toward the blue end
        of the spectrum. Basically, blue comes toward you and red moves away from you. It
        doesn't have any purpose here other than going along with the galactic theme, and
        I'm extremely nerdy; and this project is being graded so I had to include unnecessary
        crap to make excusess for using more CSS.
    </p>
    &#160;
    <h1>
        The Colors</h1>
        <div class="colorRuleWrap">
            <div id="blackRule" class="colorRule">
            </div>
            <p>
                This is a terrible, awful game. It's bad, bad, bad. Pretend it doesn't exist and
                move on with your life.</p>
        </div>
        <div class="colorRuleWrap">
            <div id="darkRedRule" class="colorRule">
            </div>
            <p>
                You could buy it, but you'll just end up using the disc as a beverage coaster.</p>
        </div>
        <div class="colorRuleWrap">
            <div id="redRule" class="colorRule">
            </div>
            <p>
                Buy it as a gift for someone you don't like.</p>
        </div>
        <div class="colorRuleWrap">
            <div id="orangeRule" class="colorRule">
            </div>
            <p>
                This is pretty bad, but you might at least get a good laugh out of how bad it is.</p>
        </div>
                <div class="colorRuleWrap">
                    <div id="yellowRule" class="colorRule">
                    </div>
                    <p>
                        Sports games.</p>
                </div>
                <div class="colorRuleWrap">
                    <div id="grayRule" class="colorRule">
                    </div>
                    <p>
                        Meh.</p>
                </div>
                <div class="colorRuleWrap">
                    <div id="greenRule" class="colorRule">
                    </div>
                    <p>
                        Put the $10 your grandma gave you for your birthday toward this one.</p>
                </div>
                 <div class="colorRuleWrap">
                     <div id="lightBlueRule" class="colorRule">
                     </div>
                     <p>
                         This is definitely worth <em>your</em> money.</p>
                 </div>
                 <div class="colorRuleWrap">
                     <div id="darkBlueRule" class="colorRule">
                     </div>
                     <p>
                         It doesn't get any better this. Except for purple, but this is really good.</p>
                 </div>
                <div class="colorRuleWrap">
                    <div id="purpleRule" class="colorRule">
                    </div>
                    <p>
                        This is a terrific, wonderful game. It's good, good, good. Buy 1000 of them, play
                        one, and build a fort with the rest.</p>
                </div>
    </section>
</body>
</html>
